=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 13=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 13 =
- Today...
- اليوم اليوم...
You go first.
اذهب أولا.
You...
أنت...
You've been different
لقد كنت مختلفا
since you came back.
منذ عودتك.
Maybe it is
ربما تكون
because I've experienced some accidents.
لأنني واجهت بعض الحوادث.
Oh,
أوه،
I just hate to see
أنا فقط أكره أن أرى
you and Lu so close.
أنت ولو قريبين جدا.
It's nothing between Lu Xingjie and me.
لا شيء بيني وبين لو Xingjie.
I don't believe it.
لا أصدق ذلك.
He just misunderstood.
لقد أساء فهمه فقط.
He had
كان لديه
a story
قصة
with my best friend abroad.
مع أعز أصدقائي في الخارج.
He thought that was me.
كان يعتقد أن هذا أنا.
So I...
لذا أنا...
So you went to the restaurant today
لذلك ذهبت إلى المطعم اليوم
just to make it clear?
فقط أن يكون واضحا؟
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
Idiot.
غبي.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Boss.
رئيس.
Sign it.
وقعها.
OK.
نعم.
Boss,
رئيس،
explain it.
اشرحها.
(Party A (Signature): Mu Liu)
(الطرف أ (التوقيع): مو ليو)
(Tang Xue, you're finally here!)
(تانغ شيويه ، أنت هنا أخيرًا!)
If you hadn't called and told me,
إذا لم تكن قد اتصلت وأخبرتني ،
I wouldn't have known
لم أكن لأعرف
that Lu Xingjie was so heartless
أن لو Xingjie كان بلا قلب
and blind.
وأعمى.
Well, if you had told him
حسنًا ، إذا أخبرته
the truth,
الحقيقة،
that wouldn't have happened, right?
ما كان ليحدث ، أليس كذلك؟
I was just afraid that he would
كنت فقط خائفة من أن يفعل ذلك
think of me as a snobbish woman.
فكر بي كامرأة متعجرفة.
But now,
لكن الآن،
I don't know how to explain it to him.
لا أعرف كيف أشرح ذلك له.
Come on.
هيا.
You just came back and you're thinking so much.
لقد عدت للتو وتفكر كثيرًا.
Put your things down.
ضع أشياءك جانبا.
Let's go to the company.
دعنا نذهب إلى الشركة.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
After a tour
بعد جولة
of the Mu's departments,
أقسام مو ،
which one do you want to go to most?
أي واحد تريد الذهاب إليه أكثر؟
If I really work here,
إذا كنت أعمل هنا حقًا ،
of course, I'll want to go to...
بالطبع ، سأذهب إلى ...
Where?
أين؟
Li,
لي ،
there's a contract
هناك عقد
that you need to deal with.
التي تحتاج إلى التعامل معها.
Lu,
لو ،
don't you see
لا ترى
that there is one more person here?
أن هناك شخصًا آخر هنا؟
You're...
أنت على...
Li, let's solve
لي ، دعنا نحل
Xia Xingrun's problem first.
مشكلة شيا Xingrun أولا.
What's wrong with him?
ماذا حل به؟
Xue,
Xue ،
don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Wait here for me.
انتظر هنا من أجلي.
So blind and heartless!
أعمى وبلا قلب!
Mr. Xia,
السيد شيا ،
your plan seriously violates
خطتك تنتهك بشكل خطير
the competition regulations.
لوائح المنافسة.
Please take it back and revise it.
يرجى إعادته ومراجعته.
Otherwise, Mr. Lu and I will never sign it.
وإلا ، فلن نوقعها أنا والسيد لو.
In business competition,
في المنافسة التجارية ،
what matters are the interests.
ما يهم هو المصالح.
Who cares what the means are?
من يهتم بما هي الوسائل؟
Mr. Lu, are you sure
السيد لو ، هل أنت متأكد
that you haven't done this before?
أن لم تفعل هذا من قبل؟
I've never done
لم افعل قط
such a dirty thing.
مثل هذا الشيء القذر.
Young man,
شاب،
don't say it so early,
لا تقلها مبكرا جدا ،
or you'll eat your words.
أو ستأكل كلامك.
There's something wrong with his development plan.
هناك شيء خاطئ في خطته التنموية.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
That's why I got you here.
لهذا السبب أتيت بك إلى هنا.
ENI is mentioned in his plan.
ايني مذكورة في خطته.
I saw the name of the company in the archives before.
رأيت اسم الشركة في الأرشيف من قبل.
You said you wanted to help me.
قلت أنك تريد مساعدتي.
I think you need my help.
أعتقد أنك بحاجة لمساعدتي.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Oh,
أوه،
I'm Li's best friend, Tang Xue.
أنا أفضل صديق لي ، تانغ شيويه.
Li?
لي؟
Eh,
إيه ،
she is
هي تكون
Mu Liu.
مو ليو.
We call her Li at school.
نسميها لي في المدرسة.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
I'll take you to her.
سآخذك إليها.
Li,
لي ،
do you find it over there?
هل تجده هناك؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
I found it!
لقد وجدته!
Here.
هنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Li,
لي ،
actually, I've been...
في الواقع ، لقد كنت ...
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Ah!
آه!
I...
أنا...
Hey!
يا!
Oh no!
أوه لا!
This is a big misunderstanding!
هذا سوء فهم كبير!
It's OK.
كل شيء على مايرام.
We didn't do anything.
لم نفعل أي شيء.
Come on!
هيا!
But,
ولكن،
why should I look for him?
لماذا يجب ان ابحث عنه؟
Looking for me?
يبحث عني؟
Yes.
نعم.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
Mo Chen,
مو تشين ،
I...
أنا...
Did Lu
هل لو
confess to you?
اعترف لك
Didn't I tell you
ألم أخبرك
that he mistook me for Xue?
أنه ظنني خطأ Xue؟
If it were me who just confessed,
لو كنت أنا من اعترف للتو ،
would you agree?
هل توافق؟
♪It's time to say your love forever♪
♪ حان الوقت لتقول حبك للأبد ♪
♪And I looking your eyes♪
♪ وأنا أنظر في عينيك ♪
♪I need you now, don't need whomever♪
♪ أحتاجك الآن ، ولست بحاجة لمن ♪
♪And l looking your heart♪
♪ وأنا أنظر إلى قلبك ♪
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪